const questions = [
    {
        question: "Who is the youngest Bridgerton sibling?",
        choices: ["Colin", "Benedict", "Hyacinth", "Gregory"],
        correct: "Hyacinth"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first to discover the identity of Lady Whistledown?",
        choices: ["Eloise Bridgerton", "Colin Bridgerton", "Daphne Bridgerton", "Genevieve Delacroix"],
        correct: "Genevieve Delacroix"
    },
    {
        question: "Who does Queen Charlotte assign the job of identifying Lady Whistledown?",
        choices: ["Daphne Bridgerton", "Penelope Featherington", "Eloise Bridgerton", "Genevieve Delacroix"],
        correct: "Eloise Bridgerton"
    },
    {
        question: "Where is Prince Friedrich from?",
        choices: ["Germany", "France", "Prussia", "Spain"],
        correct: "Prussia"
    },
    {
        question: "Who does Anthony Bridgerton marry?",
        choices: ["Kate","Sienna", "Edwina", "Cressida"],
        correct: "Kate"
    },
    {
        question: "What disorder does Lady Danbury help Simon overcome?",
        choices: ["Stuttering", "Anxiety", "Insomnia", "ADHD"],
        correct: "Stuttering"
    },
    {
        question: "How many Bridgerton siblings are there?",
        choices: ["5", "9", "6", "8"],
        correct: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "Where do Daphne and Simon first meet?",
        choices: ["At a ball", "In the park", "At a sweet shop", "At Lady Danbury's house"],
        correct: "At a ball"
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the Bridgerton's family home located?",
        choices: ["Grosvenor Square", "Regent Street", "Park Lane", "Mayfair"],
        correct: "Grosvenor Square"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Bridgerton sibling is an artist?",
        choices: ["Anthony", "Daphne", "Colin", "Benedict"],
        correct: "Benedict"
    },
    {
        question: "Who does Colin Bridgerton almost marry?",
        choices: ["Siena Rosso", "Penelope Featherington", "Marina Thompson", "Cressida Cowper"],
        correct: "Marina Thompson"
    }
];